Lindsay Haigh

lindsaytaylor925@gmail.com | 951-591-2448 | Temecula, CA 92591

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recent graduate of prolific General Assembly boot camp course with experience in teamwork, time management, software engineering and source management. Highly motivated and passionate about contributing to large software projects and looking forward to talking with you about how I can bring my skills to your organization.

WORK HISTORY

General Assembly. REMOTE

Software Engineer Teaching Assistant | 02/2022 - Current

- Tutors struggling students individually and in small groups to reinforce learning concepts.
- Aids 30 software engineering students outside of class on deliverables and projects.
- Communicates regularly with instructional team on progress of each student.

Eagle Management. REMOTE

Customer Service Representative | 04/2015 - Current

- Maintains customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Contributes to a large team effort and handles complexities arising as part of multifaceted tasks.
- Manages multiple deadlines while communicating client expectations and managing requirements.

Sam's Club. Murrieta, CA

Pharmacy Technician | 06/2013 - 01/2022

- Processed incoming drug orders by checking deliveries against paperwork and updating computer system.
- Assisted pharmacist by filling prescriptions for customers and responding to patient questions regarding prescription and medication-specific issues.

SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Node
- Express
- Bootstrap
- PostgreSQL
- Mongoose/Mongo/DB
- Python
- Source Management/Git
- TypeScript

EDUCATION

General Assembly REMOTE 01/2022

Certificate of Software Engineering

The Pharmacy Professionals Ontario, CA 08/2012

PTCB

PROJECTS

<u>Draco</u> | <u>GitHub</u> <u>Animoots</u> | <u>GitHub</u> Grubbr | GitHub